Sometimes I have bad dreams About zombies,
My dad says the nice people at Phenotrans...
made a drug called Zombrex,
If someone is bitten by a zombie,
They can take Zombrex eleven to day,
Then They stay in person,
Instead of becoming a scary monster,
Phenotrans,
stay human,
Oh shit,
No, no!
Oh yes,
East Mission, Oregon, remains under
evacuation orders at this hour,
Just moments ago,
the President authorized FEZA
to declare East Mission...
a quarantine zone.
At 10:31 this morning East Mission police...
discovered a number a suspected
of zombie attacks,
in separate, but contiguous locations.
Per standard operating procedure...
a containment wall was erected within 12 hours...
a new FEZA record,
This is the third zombie outbreak in
the United States in the last 10 years,
Most residents have evacuated the city...
as well as most civil authorities.
Unfortunately, looting has been reported...
inside the quarantine zone.
At least one biker gang is operating
in East Mission.
They are thought to be heavily armed
and extremely dangerous.
FEZA's directing all residents
who don't own cars...
to the East Mission Mega Dome...
... where they will be evacuated by bus.
Many of them are survivors of past outbreaks...
... and carry the zombie virus.
I'm gonna tell it like it is...
No, I don't want those people
getting out of there.
I don't want to be infected.
We apologize for the delay.
All individuals requiring Zombrex,
please line at least up one hour before
your scheduled injection.
Evacuation buses are expected shortly.
Again, we apologize for the delay
and thank you for your patience.
(No dialog)
Not a goddamn zombie in sight.
This is Chase Carter,
his wasting time and yours...
from False Alarmville, USA...
Any time now.
OK, let's do this.
You look beautiful.
Chase Carter here
for Hit Point Digital
reporting from inside
the quarantine zone.
Now this may well be the worst run
government operation since Katrina,
We're here at the Mega Dome
evacuation center,
where there are no buses,
no food, and no water.
The only thing people here
can be thankful for...
...is that there are as yet,
zombies don't either.
Now, many of those abandoned here...
... are survivors of past outbreaks,
Excuse me.
For them, East Mission
is a kind of community for people...
... infected with the zombie virus.
With no evacuation in sight,
they depend on the tents
behind this fence...
... and the drugs inside,
to quite literally remain human.
I'm putting myself asleep.
This story has been done.
We're not going to get a million plus hits
talking about tents.
Alright, then so let's talk about people.
Let's tell their story.
Nobody cares about these people...
... unless they're eating other people.
Fine,
You look like shit, man.
Whatever.
Mind you...
They might care about her.
Oh, com'on!
Watch me take this chick viral.
Yeah, It's always the pretty ones,
Excuse me.
Hi.
Chase Carter, Hit Point Digital.
Can I ask you a few questions?
- On camera?
-I'm not interested.
Really?
This is your chance to tell your government...
... How you feel about being abandoned.
Stuck here...
... next to them.
Anything you want to say.
Alright, fine.
Great. What's your name, again?
- Crystal.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
Crystal, do you feel your government
abandoned you?
What I think is if all these
people were not infected,
we would all be on the
bus right now.
But this is what happens.
They mess up, and we get screwed.
And then guys like you
come down here with your cameras...
... and film it make money selling
commercials. It's awesome.
Don't you think that the American people
deserve to know the truth?
The American people
don't give a shit.
Right.
You don't seem too
concerned about zombies, themselves.
You serious?
They terrify me.
Only an idiot wants to see a zombie.
That went really, really well.
I'll totally will send.
Laugh it up, but we are
the only ones with the balls...
... to cover this
thing from the inside.
So, what does that make you,
the next Frank West?
Why not?
Because he almost died.
You're gonna risk your life for this story?
- No.
But I'm willing to risk yours...
I've got an idea.
- Come on.
- God...
Com'on.
Follow me.
Shit.
Chase, no.
We are not going to get anything
from these people by embarrassing them.
We want drama,
we've got to get the needles.
No, no. I didn't come here
to explore people.
This is how we are going
to make a name for ourselves.
You know what?
Here.
What's this?
Remind yourself what real news looks like.
What it use to look like.
Real News!
Excuse me.
Hey, you alright?
Jesus Christ!
Hey!
Nurse!
Hold him.
Shit, I thought you injected.
I did.
Back, back!
Nurse! Nurse!
Nurse!
Medic!
Chase!
God hates...
Wait!
Jo!
God!
Hey!
Frank West, famously survived...
... the first zombie outbreak
in US history.
He then rose to fame with his reporting...
...on the 2006 outbreak in
Willamette, Colorado.
Frank, we don't know what's going on...
...inside East Mission yet.
How bad will it get?
Well...
Bad, Sue.
Very bad.
What do you mean by that?
Uh... I don't know,
people are going to get eaten,
faces chewed off.
Screaming, as they go down.
Their hands, arms,
guts ripped out.
People are going to be
gnawing on each other.
Eating flesh, that's what
zombies do.
Am I the only one who knows
about zombies around here?
- Yes,
- Zombies, they eat people...
Usually they start on the extremities,
usually with your fingers, hands...
- Yes, Okay?
- work their way beyond  ,
We'll be right back.
Shit.
Jesus Christ.
Hey!
Is this your van?
Yes.
Yes, it is.
Okay, listen...
We need to go, now.
Now!
But my daughter.
Jesus Christ.
Did she bit you?
She tried.
- Come on,
- She tried.
Com'on.
No no no,
We need to leave now,
We need to leave now.
- Give me the keys!
- Come on!
Let's go!
Okay, let's go.
Oh shit! Get the gate!
Get the gate!
Go! Start! Go!
Drive!
Go!
What the hell happened back there?
The drug stopped working.
Who are you calling?
My ex-boss.
I'm gonna break this story.
So the zombie body count
is up to 2,500 now.
There would be more if the golf club
hadn't broken.
Hey.
I've covered wars, you know.
And saved a lot of people in Willamette.
- Excuse me.
- Kids, mainly.
Chase, I told you, St, Louis
was a one time thing.
Screw St. Louis.
I just left the Mega Dome,
and it's funny, I didn't see any
UBN reporters around.
You're inside?
- Yeah, I am.
- UBN exclusive?
No way.
Look, I want your audience, but you've gonna
to link it back to Hit Point.
I need graphics,
now.
Stand by,
I want you live.
Hey, was your daughter taking Zombrex?
- Oh my God!
- Yes.
I make sure she takes it every single day.
Chase, did they run out of Zombrex?
No, there was plenty of Zombrex.
I saw them take it,
but they turned anyway.
I'm telling you that
Zombrex didn't work.
Startling, live reporting from Chase Carter.
Contributing reporter for...
... Hit Point Digital.
Do you know a way out?
Casey has a map.
Casey?
Casey was your daughter?
Do you think she's gonna be alright?
- Hey, watch the road!
- Look out!
Come on.
- Come on!
- Idiots.
- Hey, it's dead, it's dead.
- No! No!
Wait! Wait!
No! No!
Hey, open the gate.
Open the gate!
Open the goddamn gate!
Com'on, Jordan, pick up
the goddamn phone!
You know, instead of just standing around,
you should be looking for weapons.
A weapon?
What weapon?
This place is full of junk.
Do you need me to hold your
hand for everything?
Make one.
- Use lethal force if necessary.
- What?
The virus could be airborne.
Airborne?
If anyone gets out,
it can kill millions.
Jesus.
Are you crazy?
You, go back.
You can't come out.
What? No.
Turn around now.
No.
Walk.
- Now.
- Come on.
Listen, I'm not going back out there.
Help!
- Help!
- Wait! Let us in!
Shit.
Close the gate!
Watch her.
- No! No!
- Wait! Help us!
- Let me in!
- Come on, let us out!
Come on, open the gate.
- Please, let us in!
- Now!
Chase, where the hell were you?
I was 15 feet from the goddamn car.
You left me.
No, listen, they were all over me.
I couldn't see you.
Where are you now?
In some pawnshop downtown.
- Are you out?
- Come on, let us in!
- Please!
- Open the gate!
Yes, I just got through.
- Help!
Jo?
What's going on?
I don't know.
Turn back!
Open up the gate.
Get away from the wall, now,
I have orders to shoot.
- Open up this goddamn thing now!
- Let us in!
Come on! This is my family right here.
Jesus, What are you doing?
The virus is airborne,
they could kill us,
This is your last chance,
get away from the wall.
Open up, please. Open up the gate!
Take her to quarantine.
Wait! What does he mean?
Com'on, please,
my family, save us.
Dad!
Wait!
Jo, you still there?
Chase,
Chase...
They shot people.
They're shooting people.
Listen, you gotta get me out.
I don't...
I don't think I can.
Wait.
We should stay here tonight.
There's no where to go, anyway.
Why not?
They're shooting people at the wall.
We're trapped.
Authorities now suspect that
the East Mission virus is...
... resistance to Zombrex.
Some media outlets are reporting
that may communicable ...
... through touch or some kind
of airborne contact.
In response FEZA stopped all
evacuation efforts...
... and have sealed the city.
For a view from inside,
go again by
Hit Point's, Chase Carter.
Chase,
Those rumors are
completely false, Susan.
I'm with a small group...
... right now, and we're all fine.
If you can pass
the virus by touch...
... or by some airborne transmission,
we'd know it.
Are you sure you're not infected?
I have no symptoms, the people
I'm with have no symptoms, we're fine.
Do you feel the  government
has abandoned you?
You're damn right I do.
What right do they have
to keep us here?
Frank, does the Government have
the right...
... quarantine our corespondent?
It's a zombie apocalypse,
And you're talking about right?
Jesus Christ!
Chase, Where I'm I look...? Chase.
Hey, listen,
you just keep reporting, OK?
You're doing a good
job in there, my man.
Alright, Frank, let's get back...
... to the topic at hand.
I'm sure that the government is...
... working hard on a fix.
The government is working hard
on not shitting it's pants.
If this is a resistant strain...
... they're going to burn everyone.
OK, we don't know that
they are going to burn anyone.
- No...
- We don't want to cause panic out there  ,
What are you talking about?
If you're on the inside of this one, ah, shit,
You are really fucked.
OK. Fantastic.
Celebrity isn't going to
get you out of here.
Making people care might.
Drink.
Thanks.
Hey, Maggie.
Look,  know it might be hard.
But can I interview you?
I don't know...
I don't think that I have anything to say.
Well you know,
sharing your story...
... it might help you with
what happened to your daughter.
OK.
Great.
Go ahead.
Casey, she...
You have to understand that her dad...
... left us right after she was bitten.
He...
...blamed me, I guess.
I was in the kitchen when it happened.
I got two of them.
But the third one...
... got to her crib.
It didn't do much damage.
You can barely see the scar,
I just...
I don't get to her in time.
So, it's just her and me now.
And she's not lust my daughter,
she is my best friend,
And we struggled...
Well we still struggle.
But we get by.
And it makes us stronger.
You know, closer.
Even when she isn't in
the same room as me...
She is all I can think of.
I can't wait for you to met her.
She is such a wonderful little child.
I'm going to feel much better
when I get to her.
You should eat.
You've got to keep up your strength.
Turn around, and put
your hands on your head.
- Okay, just calm down,
- Do it now!
I'm not infected!
Turn around, and put
your hands on your head.
- OK!
- Now!
Stop.
Just relax.
I would like to save at
least one person today.
Hey, you know how to use one of these?
Yeah.
You want to tell me what's going on?
We think it is a resistant strain.
The evacuation is closed
until we know for sure.
You were the last person
through the gate
And if it is positive?
Let's hope that's not the case.
- Hey.
- Jordan...
...I'm with a girl,
and she is infected.
Well, I'm sitting in a
plastic room...
... waiting for them to decide if
they are going to shoot me or not.
Is she showing symptoms?
I saw her shooting up Zombrex.
And it worked.
That proves that
it isn't a resistant strain.
So, her drug is different?
She's different?
Either way, that girl is evidence.
It's a huge story.
A story that could kill me in my sleep.
Oh come Chase!
She is still human.
She's probably terrified.
And given the panic here, she
is your best shot...
... To convince FEZA to left her out.
Then, you need to stay with her.
All I have to do is get her on camera.
If I can get something,
can you get me out?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll do everything I can.
And Chase...
... just make sure you know how
exactly how much she has left, okay?
Yeah.
Hey?
Hi.
Here.
Thank you.
My daughter has one just like it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Don't worry, I'm going.
It's OK.
I know how it feels.
Casey and I have to
deal with it every day.
But you're not alone.
I always tell Casey that
in situations like these...
...that you have to
hold on to your friends.
They're not easy to find.
Well...
Thank you, but...
...I've got to go.
I'm almost out of time.
You're clear.
And I'm guessing that it's your truck,
messing up my camp.
Hey!
It's not a resistant strain.
Yeah, where did you go to medical school?
My partner is in there.
One of the people he's with has her
own Zombrex and she is fine.
How do I know that?
Send a copter,
bring them out and test her.
Meanwhile...
I have a whole quarantine to run.
Researchers across the country
are working on that.
Meanwhile you are shooting people.
- Healthy people.
- You think I like that?
You think I want that?
I am responsible for the
safety of the entire country.
I can't take a chance,
... on them,
on your friend.
You want to give me proof?
You better make it quick.
Go, go, go!
- Yes, sir,
- On the left side  ,
- On me.
- Yes sir,
New developments in the
Mission East quarantine...
The US military arrived,
and we go now live
to a press conference.
already in progress,
Citizens, we are here to
support FEZA in any way we can.
This is a serious situation,
but there is no need to panic,
It is true,
tough choices have to be made.
and they will be taken,
and they will be made decisively.
I have been authorized
by the White House...
... to destroy the threat,
through military action.
This country is and will remain safe,
I expect fire bombing to commence...
... within 48 hours,
Thank you for your time.
Frank, what advice do you have...
... for those trapped in
inside the quarantine zone?
Turn off your television.
Put down your phones and
run for your goddamn life.
Run where?
The quarantine is sealed,
there is nowhere to go.
What the hell are you talking about?
Fine, Let me tell you something.
- Read my book.
- Oh, Jesus  ,
Chapter 5,
I specifically tell you that...
... can't worry about technicalities.
Okay? Screw the rules.
You have to improvise,
think on your feet...
... use what you can,
where you can.
Maybe you shoot you down
like a dog, maybe not,
But I'll tell you one thing...
Talking to us,
ain't going to help you at all.
Sorry.
I didn't realize.
You don't owe me anything.
How are you feeling?
Hey?
Why do your drugs work and theirs didn't?
I have a dealer.
I hate those goddamn clinics.
You have any left?
Just one.
Do you know where to get more?
Oh thank God!
I thought you left me here.
Look, We need to stick together and
come up with some kind of plan.
Yeah, well, I don't have time, so...
... I have to find some Zombrex...
... out there.
is true.
Tough choices must be made.
Will be made.
And they will be made decisively.
I have been authorized
by the White House...
... to destroy the threat,
through military action.
I expect firebombing
to commence within 48 hours.
Come on.
We've got five minutes, boys!
Get what you can!
Let's go shopping.
Yeah!
Take everything!
Yeah.
You're gonna get us killed.
You're a bad girl, huh?
Look at you.
Yeah. Okay, okay...
- You've got me.
- Leave the sword.
Logan!
Now.
Move.
Yeah.
I found my sword.
Maybe they can help us.
- I don`t believe...
- You can trust me, I've got this.
- Honey, wait!
- Hey...
Hey, hold up!
Hey, guys.
Oh, Jesus.
Thank God.
We can go with you guys?
Please man, just...
We need help, man.
It's OK, yeah, yeah.
Ten grand, one way.
What?
I don't have $10,000.
You should have just offered me the girl.
Now I get her for free.
- Fuck,
- Run!
Run! Run!
Oh shit.
Get off me!
Yeah!
No! No! Come back!
Stop! Get off of me!
- You want a ride?
- Yes!
Help! Please help me!
You should have ran.
No!
No! Help me!
Please don't leave me!
Frank, our producers
would like to know...
...If you can give
our viewers...
... especially, our
younger viewers...
Yeah, word up.
Some tips on
how to deal with zombies,
- Of course,
- Before you answer,
let's go back to Willamette.
What you saw,
what you felt,
what did you do...
... when you were confronted
for many zombies at once?
Well the first thing you want to do is
take out as many as possible,
Early.
So go for the weak ones first.
Grandma...
... take her out, grandpa too.
You've got siblings?
They're going to be easier.
Save your parents for the last.
Remember to breathe,
Take short breaks...
... to recover your stamina.
And then when you get down to the last one...
... or two...
... probably your mom or dad...
You should be OK.
Just make sure you finish the job.
Frank, that's...
Wow, thank you. That was great.
Hey, and one more thing, kids.
Remember to build weapons.
Lots of weapons.
Maggie, would you get some tape?
Help me.
You coming?
Listen.
The only reason they are bombing
is they don't know you exist.
They didn't know your drugs is working.
We don't need to go out there.
We just need to get you on camera.
Not happening.
Your daughter isn't out there.
Good luck.
Damn!
Jordan,I have an idea.
Now, listen to me.
I need you to find some Zombrex.
Great.
Shit.
Goddammit!
Okay, we have to
do it quietly.
It's okay,
Hey!
You ready to die,
you brain dead zombies fucks?
Come and get it!
Chase! That's enough.
Follow us.
Motherfucker!
Com'on.
Thanks.
Get in.
Hey, right now,
real quick, pop quiz.
How would you kill me
if you could?
Oh my God!
Right now, with my bare hands.
You would lose against a zombie.
BAd advice, don't try it with
bare hands, grab a weapon.
Can I tell you how I would kill you?
- I wouldn't
- You're killing me right now.  ,
Wouldn't, I wouldn't kill you.
If you were a zombie, I'd let you eat me.
Oh God!
- This seems like a great place to...
- I'm kidding!
I'm kidding. I would smash your
head in with a television.
I would smash your head in with that television right there.
I may be begging you to do that shortly.
Do you still have Zombrex
stored inside the city?
- I'm very busy.
- Do you have supplies in there or not?
Why? So you can blame this on us?
So I can save lives.
How are you going to do that?
I need to get some Zombrex
to a guy inside.
I can prove that it's
not a resistant strain.
Counts and estimates.
We show have a look,
- But General, she's not...
- Don't worry.
I was here.
- Listen...
- No!
Norton, you've got to help me out.
Excuse me.
Jesus.
Thank you, Norton.
Got it.
Hey, I think I can get them to let us out.
Hey, did you hear me?
Okay.
They've all been looted.
Jordan found something.
A storage facility. There should be Zombrex there.
Come on, let's go.
Who the hell did this?
I don't know.
Think they're still home?
Thanks.
Jesus Christ.
How are we supposed to find
anything in here?
Come on.
You be my friend?
You want to be my friend...
My friend?
Let's play a game.
Hey where's Maggie?
Okay, let's go,
Is anyone living here?
Son of a bitch.
It's the same shit
from the stadium.
We still have to prove
the problem is with the drugs.
and not a new strain
of the virus.
Really, how?
You take a dose.
If symptoms come on, we know
it doesn't work.
and then you can take
good stuff right away.
Are you kidding?
If we can prove the drugs is bad,
and go public,
they will have to let us out.
Yeah, go public.
Look, we can search every
drug store in town.
We still get firebombed tomorrow.
It's the only way.
Take your camera.
My friend... My friend.
Let's play a game.
Game... Game... Game,
my friend.
Will you be my friend...
My friend?
Will you be my friend?
Be My Friend?
Be my friend...
I'm sorry.
Mommy's here.
Oh baby, I'm sorry.
I love you.
You're my friend.
This is Chase Carter,
recording Crystal LaRourke.
Crystal,
can you bring the vial to the camera?
This is the same batch that
they were using tn the Mega Dome yesterday.
As you can see...
... it has no effect.
Now this is her personal supply.
not government issue.
Go ahead, Crystal.
Crystal!
Help me.
Shit.
You alright?
Yeah.
Oh shit!
What?
We're trapped.
Frank...
We are here to talk about your
experience at Willamette...
and to hopefully offer people some kind of advice,
- or hope...
- How much hope do they have?
You're basically, are fucked.
I'm sorry, but you are...
That's great.
Your book must have been one page.
"You're basically fucked" is
all it said.
No, it's a lot of pages.
You must be  "fucked" a hundred times?
-It's...
- Okay, so that's it  ,
Let's take a break...
... this informative chat with Frank West.
has a lot more pages, it doesn't
say that. It has tons of words.
You think Maggies OK?
There you go.
Give me your phone.
Why?
Hey wait, don't have to do that.
You know, after Fortune City,
everyone was so happy
me that I had survived, you know?
But...
... that all change really quickly.
My friends started avoiding me,
my coworkers,
I was clerking at
a law firm,
and I spent my
last week in the basement.
My fiance,
he stuck around for 33 days.
That was when I started hiding.
I feel like that's...
all I've done in
the last five years.
Stay alive,
but not really living.
There is no point to hiding it now,
so maybe it will help someone.
Who's...
Chris Krabowski?
I changed my name.
Yeah, I...
figured if I wanted to get famous,
I needed to change my name.
Not many stars out
there named Krabowski.
Oh my God!
Well...
Since you fought off a horde
of zombies single handily,
you'll gonna be bigger than Frank West.
Yeah.
This is Chase Carter,
recording Crystal LaRourke.
The dramatic video by UBN correspondent, Chase Carter...
... raises serious questions about
government management of this disaster.
Oh my God!
That video is amazing.
We have 3 million hits already...
UBN is running it like every 3 minutes.
Are they letting people out?
I'm going to talk to FEZA about it,
right now.
Doesn't matter.
At least I don't think it's going to matter.
What? No, listen,
listen, Just hang in there.
We're trapped.
I don't know how much time we have left.
Don't you give up on me, Chase.
Listen, no matter what happens.
Don't beat yourself up, OK?
You're a good friend, Jordan.
You bastard, don't
even think about it.
Chase?
Goodbye, Jo.
You want to call someone?
Come on, let's go, boys.
Who left open the goddamn
zombie room open?
Any last words?
You've got to be kidding me.
The drugs don't work.
I mean, I could chain you up there with Larry.
- Son of...
- Yeah, I know.
Would you can clean up this mess?
I'm sorry, sir, but
I can't confirm that.
Get the hell out of my tent.
My guy is
trapped in your warehouse.
He needs help right away,
Yeah Yeah, screw your guy and his help.
I'm buried under 10 tons of shit...
... you guys stirred up with that video.
They're going kill him,
Yes, and not just him.
Get the hell out. Go.
If he dies, I'm coming for you.
Hey!
Don't worry, I'm from the press.
- Crystal?
- I don't think we should...
This proves that it is safe
to let people out.
Okay.
But I'm not running this quarantine.
Not yet, anyway.
What do we have to do
to get him out?
Personally,
I'm more concerned the thousands of
people trapped in there with him.
People that I
have been ordered to kill.
What are you suggesting?
Nothing.
- Okay.
- Mind you...
...If I was in charge,
my first order would be to
send in a combat team...
... to rescue that girl
and anyone with her.
Now if you'll excuse me.
I have a press conference.
Shit.
Well, well, well.
There's my little bad girl.
Bring that ass to me.
Hey!
The dramatic video by
UBN correspondent, Chase Carter...
... raises serious questions about...
... FEZA's management of the disaster.
We now go live to a
joint press conference...
... just outside the quarantine wall.
We are presently conducting an exhaustive audit...
... on our supply system.
So far we have
no reason to suspect...
In spite of the evidence,
you deny your drugs are bad?
We're still investigating that video.
You are perfectly aware
the veracity of that video.
You asked for proof, and Chase Carter...
... risked his life
to get you that proof.
And now you would rather let
a lot of innocent people die,
- to admit you screwed up.
- My priority...
...is the safety of this country.
We contained an outbreak.
This quarantine is a success.
General...
... does this look like a success to you,?
Miss, when knee deep in shit,
you should be happy
it's not up to your neck...
... But you're still knee deep in shit.
Tonight we bear witness ...
... to the death of a great American city.
A city that was your job to save.
Yes, I can think of a lot of words
to describe this situation,
but "success", is not one of them.
How was the outbreak spread?
Was it airborne?
What the hell?
Hey...
You can't leave me here like this!
Hey!
Turn that up, pretty boy.
That's my jam!
Son of a bitch!
This is good,
this is good!
Shut up!
Son of a bitch.
Seriously,
come on.
Come on, Chase,
you can you do this.
Yes.
Come here, stupid zombie.
Yes, Are you hungry?
Here you go.
You're ruining it.
Eat him.
The Congress today passed Bill HR251...
... handing complete control
to the East Mission quarantine ...
... to the military.
Some Congressmen are already
calling for an investigation...
... into FEZA's embarrassing performance.
We have sent a team to the warehouse.
There's nobody there but zombies.
What?
You did your best.
More than most people would.
I'm sorry.
For what it's worth...
... we're restarting the evacuation.
You have saved a lot of lives.
(No Dialog)
Chase?
Chase! Oh my God!
Where were you?
- Are you here?
- I'm at the warehouse.
I got out.
At the...
but they said...
Helicopters, did you see any helicopter?
No, I didn't see any helicopter.
The army was suppose to go
in there and get you out.
Yeah, well obviously they don't care.
Look, If I can make it to
the wall, can I get out?
Yeah, you can get out.
Something is not alright here.
- What isn't?
- Just trust me...
When you get here, don't tell anyone
who you are, you understand?
Not you, not that girl.
... You, you've got balls,
I'll give you that.
A man needs
a girl to point...
... a gun to his head every once in awhile.
Yeah? Lend me yours and
I can do it again.
This is gonna hurt.
Yes? Good,
I like it rough.
You know, I saw you on the news.
You came in here after
the wall went up.
That takes balls.
There's no law.
No order.
The place was practically begging me.
And the zombies, don't scare you?
Brother Z?
No.
No, I've got pit bulls that cause me
more trouble than that.
Help!
You think I'm that stupid?
You gonna wish I killed you.
Look around.
You're are already dead.
Not me.
What, you're gonna blow us all up?
Maybe...
Maybe I will,
or maybe...
I'll just blow up that wall out there.
And that's your plan to get out?
Who said I wanted out?
I'm king of this shit,
Before all this,
I was just a nine to fiver...
... I was trying to
get through the goddamn day.
My life meant nothing.
I was nothing.
But now...
Now?
It's a paradise,
But now...
... now they want to go, and bomb it.
Right?
But...
What if it is too
big to bomb?
See, it got me thinking.
What if...?
Mr. Z out for a walk.
Expand his horizons.
But...
See now...
The old Z...
old Z can't do it on his own.
No no no no,
But me and Z?
Me and Z, got what you
call "a mutual interest".
So, no!
No! No!
I don't want out of this shit!
I'm taking this shit with me!
Get on your knees...
Now!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What are you going to do?
Huh? What are you going to do?
King of the fucking Zombies!
No! No!
No!
Todd get that bitch!
Where are you going? Huh?
Where are you going?
You bitch!
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
- Come on.
- Yes!
No!
What? You're not done
with her yet?
No, I'm not done with her yet.
I'm gonna rip every little piece...
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Kill her.
Come on.
Get off!
No!
Nooooooo!
Nice swing.
Drive, Krabowski.
As we count down the hours...
... for the inevitable, tragic
firebombing of Mission East...
...we now join General Lyons...
... for this important update.
For more than a year,
we have worked very closely
with Phenotrans...
... to improve how we treat infected people.
When survivors pass
through this gate,
we will implant them with these.
This chip contains year supply...
... of highly concentrated Zombrex.
No more daily shots.
No more human error.
No more tragedies like this one.
- Is Phenotrans involved?
- Thank you.
- You use Zombrex every day?
- Every day.
I want you to take
this and wait over there.
Get the hell away from me.
I know you're pissed at
me, and you have every right to be.
I did what I did to save my friend.
Oh, you lied on national TV,
and you cost me my career.
Why would I be pissed?
I didn't lie.
I never sent you to that warehouse.
You put a note on my car.
No, I didn't.
Son of a bitch.
Lyons...
- He screwed us both.
- Yeah.
Me, more than you...
So what the hell is going on?
Okay, look...
Phenotrans came to us
years ago with these chips.
It was a civil rights nightmare,
obviously.
So we passed.
Now look what's happened.
The Army has been set up to
take over Homeland Defense.
Lyons is a frick'in hero.
and they can put these computer chips
in who ever they feel like.
How do I fix this?
Okay, look.
Does your kid have any
other information from the warehouse?
He's got pictures.
Wait a minute.
Check it out,
The Army already had those chips
on their trucks when they arrived.
That's not even the half of it.
It's okay.
Thanks.
Hey,
I'm leaving and I just thought
maybe I could...
... get some closure on
Chase before I left.
I'm sorry about him.
Thanks.
Listen, can  I talk to the
officer who led that mission?
I think it would make me feel better
knowing what he saw.
That off the books mission
I did it as a favor...
I'm sorry, I can't do that.
I know.
I'm just trying to make sure
I did everything I could,
But you said he did make
a difference and I think...
I think he would
like that.
That line of survivors out there
proves that.
Let me add something personal.
I came here with orders
to wipe this place out.
But instead...
... my boys...
...are out there handing out blankets!
And hot meals.
Every one of them,
me in particular...
...owe that to him.
And you.
You've had enough time to get
the new chips here?
This is the US Army,
darling.
When lives are on the line,
we move pretty damn fast.
That's a welcome change.
And Phenotrans, they can move up?
Well, they are not military,
they're not bad.
With three or four days warning.
They get the job done.
Three or four days?
Thanks.
Survivors would
only need...
... to refill the drug
once a year,
Would anyone who has this
disease not want that?
Maybe they wouldn't want to be tracked...
... by the army 24/7.
Reading their vital signs,
tracking their movements.
You want the
Army to know...
... every time you're
taking a dump, Sue? Come on!
The Army is not tracking
every time I take a dump, Frank.
- You don't know that.
- This is ridiculous.
The only thing they will be tracking...
...is if you need more drugs,
- Really?
- Yes.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Because most people...
... can't be trusted to remember...
... when their life saving drug,
is about to run out.
But what if does more than that?
What if it listens to your
phone calls?
Knows who you're talking too,
knows what you are talking about?
- Knows if you're about to protest something,
- You're crazy.
What happens when they don't like
what you're doing,
come to your house in
a unmarked van...
throw you in the back and take you
to a secret base in Uzbekistan...
... where they will hook up
electrodes to your ball sack...
... and make you talk?
- Frank...
- That's a fact  ,
- No
- Google it...
That's is simply, bat shit crazy.
Well, they've called me
that since Willamette.
But guess what?
I'm still here.
We have Bravo team
guest estimate at one kilometer.
Make sure we have
some guys on roofs.
Okay, we have a lookout
in the northwest corner too.
Hey.
So, Phenotrans need
three or four days...
... to get those
chips to the military.
So, how did the bastards have
them when they arrived?
Exactly.
Wait, your friend
has got the FEZA waybill...
...straight to the warehouse.
But no one at FEZA
has heard of him.
Let's see if the military has.
Norton,
look at you.
Yeah,
show me that waybill.
Those fuckers!
The shipment came from Fort Carson.
That's General Lyons base.
Sit tight, The world got to see this.
Hey, wait...
No! No!
Please! Please!
Shit.
Tear it apart, if you have too.
Check everywhere.
Chase,
the army planted
the bad Zombrex in there.
So track the label of that case
you took the picture of.
If you can't find me,
it will lead to them.
Halt! Get down! Get down!
On the ground, now!
Check her out, check her!
Leave your vehicle.
Walk towards the wall, slowly.
Keep your hands where
we can see them.
They're not going to shoot us?
No, we're gonna be fine.
Oh, shit.
Come on!
Turn down the radio.
I'm sorry, what?
Turn off the radio now!
Okay.
We need to see those hands.
Your hands, let me see them.
Step away from the vehicle.
- Is everything OK?
- Step away from the vehicle!
Yeah, Yeah.
Step away from the vehicle, now!
No problem!
I lost the target!
I can't see!
Conserve your ammo,
wait for targets.
Come on,
boys and girls.
Welcome...
... to the after party,
to the party!
Is that's a fucking bomb?
Son of a bitch.
Go.
- I think I see movement.
- Open fire!
Come on!
Crystal!
Bomb!
- Bomb!
- Withdrawal!
Withdrawal!
Clear the area.
Crystal!
The bomb!
Go!
This is gonna hurt!
Run!
Is this a secure line?
Yes, sir,It is,
You've done well, General.
Public pressure has worked
just as you predicted.
I believe we have help
congress and the press...
... To better understand
their priorities, sir,
I have the go order in my hand.
You have your green light, Lyons.
Thank you, General Hemlock.
We are T minus five minutes.
You okay?
Yeah, are we done?
Almost.
Hey, you mind if I plug this in?
The battery is low.
Well, I guess you must
be pretty happy.
Finally got your big story.
I'm happy we got out alive.
Thank you,
Krabowski.
Sorry, I've gotta...
I haven't been able to find Jordan nowhere.
Yeah, Go.
I wanted to thank her.
I'll be right back.
This will only sting for a moment.
What?
And in three, two, one.
We're up.
Gentlemen,
Project Watchtower ...
...is now online.
Good job!
Today, America breathes
a sigh of relief.
We survived.
And there is every reason to hope...
... this is the last time
we will face such a crisis.
There is no reason
to believe that at all.
The zombie virus is out there...
...waiting, resting,
rethinking it's strategy.
When it's ready,
it will be back.
All we can do is...
... hope we are ready too.
Thank you, Frank.
Coming up next,
celebrity dogs.
Celebrity dogs.
Come on, Jordan, pick up.
Chase...
The army planted
bad Zombrex in there.
The tracking label on that crate
you took a picture of.
If you can't find me,
will lead you to them.
- What's that?
- It's. ah...
Real news.
Sky Captain, this is Zulu-2
approaching target.
Roger, Zulu-2,
weapons are free.
Roger, Sky Captain,
starting the run now.